- Where's the money?
- You've already
been paid in full.
- Deal has changed.
I want everything.
- I don't think so.
- Gracias .
- Hola, Papi.
- How was your day?
- The usual.
- Usual?
Hey, baby.
- Okay.
- I've got a party
here next week
for some prospective
business partners,
and I'd like you to attend.
- Do I have to?
- Yes.
- No, no!
- Who are you talking with?
- Ah, nobody. No!
Oy, Papa .
- Felipe.
- No, no.
- Felipe?
- Ciao.
Eh.
- Pa.
- Your mother was so
good at this stuff.
I'm not. You know that.
Hey, babe, wait.
- Yeah, I can see
that you're a caveman.
- Yes, I am, the worst.
And it always help having
beauty around, like you.
- So I wouldn't be there
because of my brain?
- Yes.
- Or my razor-sharp wit.
- Yes, you can bring them.
Just maybe don't
deploy them, okay?
Is that a yes?
- Mm.
- Is that a yes?
- Sure.
But you owe me.
- Ciao, Carlos .
- Okay, sir, it
is time to close.
- Have you tried this cake?
- Uh,
I like it a lot.
I take a piece home
when there is leftover.
- Have you tried this cake?
- No.
Not today, sir.
Uh, uh, mm, not this one.
- Have you given yourself
a gift this week,
Alex?
- I'm sorry sir,
but I have to close.
Sit.
- Listen to me.
You must learn to give
yourself a gift once a week.
Life is shorter than you think.
And small things are the
ones that really matter.
- Please don't hurt me.
- Open.
Ah.
- Mm.
- It's good?
Thank you, Alex.
- Get out.
Now!
- I can take you home, Alex.
- No! Puta.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Wiping now.
Shit.
- Ah! No, what the fuck!
Oh, help me!
Ah! Ah!
- You.
You were the breach,
the chink in the armor.
You opened the door
and she was taken.
Who was he?
- Mm.
What did he look like?
- And you expect me to
believe that a homeless bum,
whose face you couldn't see,
walks across the street
from the local fucking food bank
and decide to single-handedly
take out two armed bodyguards.
I want every goddamn gangbanger,
hustler,.
A significant sum.
- Ah! Stop!
Stop!
Ah, stop the car!
- Ah. Ah!
- Hey! Hey!
Hey, stop running!
- Ah, no! Ah.
Help!
- I just wanna talk to you, okay
Hey!
Stop running.
Hey, stop running.
All right, calm down.
Stop running, okay?
You speak English?
- Yes!
- You, you thirsty?
- I'm not drinking that. You're
probably trying to drug me.
- I'm not trying to drug you.
It's there if you want it.
And don't run anywhere, okay?
I just.
I want you to see something.
You see that?
- Hmm.
- Take a look. Okay?
Take a look at it.
I was friends with your mother.
That was before you were born.
- Congratulations.
But right now, you're
a psychotic kidnapper.
You locked me in
the trunk of a car!
You're a fucking lunatic!
- Calm down, calm down.
I'm not here to hurt you.
- I don't trust you.
- You can trust me. Look at me.
Your mother, she sent
me here to come get you.
- Bullshit.
My mother has been
dead for five years!
- I know.
Your mother made me promise
if anything ever
happened to her,
that I would find you
and I would come and take
you away from Vicente.
- What keep you?
- It's a long story.
Look, I'm sorry I locked you
in the trunk of the car, okay?
I didn't have a choice.
I just needed to get as
much distance between us
and the city as possible.
I'm sorry about that,
but I'm telling you the truth.
- Prove it!
- I will, later.
But right now, we need to
get back inside that car.
- I'm not going
anywhere with you.
- Please.
- No.
- Goddamnit.
Okay.
- You might as
well shoot me here,
but I'm not getting
back in the car!
- You take the gun.
Look, I'm putting
the gun on the floor.
All right, the gun's yours.
You can take it.
You can sit in the
back seat if you want
and keep the gun trained
at me the whole time.
I won't even look at
you if you don't want.
But we need to get back
inside that car right now!
What? You wanna stay out
here the whole night?
Come on, take the gun!
- You want me to believe that
this is loaded? Fuck yourself.
- Pull the trigger.
Jesus Christ!
Okay, you believe me now?
- Now, get back in
the car right now.
Now, take me back home.
- It's not happening.
- Yes, it is. Turn
the car or I'll shoot.
- We both know you're
not gonna shoot anybody.
Now, just sit back, calm down.
It's gonna be a long drive.
- You said my mother asked you
to take me from Vicente, my dad.
So that means you
know who he is, right?
- Oh yeah, I know exactly
who that son of a bitch-
- Yeah, and rich
and powerful man.
And when you're a
rich and powerful man,
you protect what's yours,
which mean lessons of
firearms for everyone,
especially his little girl.
- Okay.
- Now, turn the car
around or I'll shoot!
- You're
gonna shoot me?
Really? In cold blood?
- Yeah.
- I don't think so.
- Don't test me. I'll do it.
- Oh yeah, you're gonna do it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- You think so?
Go on then.
- I'm not scared of you.
- Knock yourself out.
What the fuck? Are you crazy?
Jesus Christ! What
are you doing?
- Oh, I see! You put an empty
shell in the mag, asshole!
- You're actually
gonna try and kill me?
- Dude, you kidnapped me.
You're probably going
to rape me and kill me.
Of course, I fucking
tried to kill you.
Asshole!
- Give me that!
Jesus Christ.
- Fuck yourself!
- The hell is wrong with you?
- Oh, fucking great.
Shit!
Okay, now listen to me.
I'm not here to hurt you, okay?
You understand that?
I'm just gonna put
some gas in the car.
I'm gonna be quick, and
then we're outta here.
Look at me.
Don't do anything stupid.
I'm watching you.
Hey!
- Hey, guys, guys, guys.
She's, whatever the girl
just said, don't believe her.
She's, uh, she's crazy, loca .
Loca, loca, crazy.
I don't want any trouble.
You speak English?
Hey, I don't speak Spanish.
Hey, don't come any closer.
You speak English?
Hey, back off!
Don't! Back off!
All right, I don't
wanna have to do that.
Hey, leave it, no!
Don't!
Back off.
Back off!
Back off right now or I'm
gonna break his fucking arm.
I'll do it. I'll do it!
Shit.
I told you I didn't want
to fight. Now, back off!
- Back off!
Fuck this.
- Dad! Dad!
Dad, he kidnapped me!
- Hey, come here.
- Fuck!
- Elisa, Elisa!
Elisa!
- Come here. Walk.
Look, look. You see
this carnage right here?
You see this? That's on you.
I didn't wanna have
to hurt those guys,
but you forced my hand.
And you get in the
fucking car. Get in there!
Hey, come here. Come here.
- Don't touch me! Fuck you!
- Get off it! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me.
Goddamnit!
- Get off me! Fuck you!
- Turn around!
- Ah, fuck you!
Ah!
- You sit still!
- Fuck you!
- Hey, stop it.
Don't kick me. Stop it!
You wanna go back inside
the trunk? Stop it.
- Who are you to
tell me what to do?
Fuck you!
- I'm your father!
I'm your real father.
- Bullshit.
I'm hungry.
Look,
when I'm stressed, tired,
and angry, I get
really, really hungry.
And right now, I'm all of
those things to the max.
So if I don't get food
soon, I'm going to lose my
fucking temper!
- Okay, fine. Stop it.
Jesus Christ, this is you
before you lose your temper?
- Your call, kidnapper.
- Okay. Don't kick the chair.
- Nick.
- Speak.
- Girl got grabbed.
She's in the wind.
This morning.
It's an opportunity.
This makes us even then?
- Does it?
- All right, come on.
Need to get moving.
Eliza, you need to eat up fast.
- It's Elisa.
- What?
- Elisa.
- Alisa?
- E.
- Elisa, okay. Sorry.
Are you gonna eat
the whole thing?
Come on. We need to go.
- I need to eat.
You locked me in
the trunk for hours.
I'm finishing this or I'm
screaming the place out.
- Okay.
- Let's just
speculate for a moment
that you're not
completely full of shit
that you're actually my father.
So do this, Daddy,
where have you been
my entire life?
- It's, uh, complicated.
- How complicated?
- I was in prison,
all right? 15 years.
- So you're a criminal?
- No, no, I'm not a criminal.
They let me out, okay?
- You beat the shit out of
my drivers and kidnapped me.
So yeah, you're
still a criminal.
- Shit.
- What were
you in there for?
- Does it matter?
- What's your name anyway?
- Kris.
- Kris?
- Yeah, Kris. Something
wrong with Kris?
- It's funny that my
daddy's named Kris.
- Alisa.
- Elisa.
- Elisa. Okay, Elisa?
All right, sorry.
- Thank you.
What?
- I was just thinking how much
you look like your mother.
- Yeah.
I don't look like you at all.
- No, you don't,
but I'm pretty sure
you inherited my temper.
- I miss her so much.
I don't know why she-
- She didn't.
I think Vicente killed her.
- Why would you say
that? You're a liar.
He'll never do
something like that.
- He says that you can
sit tight or die right now.
- Tell him the, uh, safety's on.
- Elisa!
Hey.
Where are they taking her?
You speak English?
- Fuck you!
- Oh, you speak English.
You're gonna tell me
where they're taking her
or I'm gonna bash
your fucking face in.
You understand me?
- Fuck you!
- Okay.
- Talk!
Ready to talk now?
- Puta !
- Slick.
Gracias .
Mm?
- Okay.
- Elisa .
- Yes.
- Are you okay ?
- Did he hurt you ?
- No.
- Hey,
I have something to ask
you, something important.
- Yes ?
- Do you have anything
to do with Mama's death?
- Of course not.
I did everything
I could for her.
I still don't know why
she did what she did.
I love her like I love you.
- He says that he's
my real father.
- Papa.
Hello, Papa.
Papa!
- It seems we have a
rival for your reward.
Come on. Come on.
- Fuck!
- Hide there if you want to
live, come on.
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Ah, no no no.
- Elisa!
- No!
- Run!
- Fuck!
Shit.
- Get outta here! Go!
- Die, motherfucker!
- Ah!
- Kris, Kris, Kris.
- Come on. Come on.
Move! Let's go!
Stop. Stop.
- Are you okay?
- What about you? You okay?
Did they hurt you?
- No.
Who was that psycho?
- I don't know, but he kicked
the shit outta me.
- Shit.
How do you learn to
fight like that, huh?
- I used to get punched
in the face for a living.
Thanks for saving
my ass back there, okay?
- Think you saved me.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Gracias .
- You talked about how bad
Vicente treated my mother.
I don't remember it like that.
- Your mom was a strong
woman, all right?
She wouldn't have
wanted you to know
that her life was a living hell.
Vicente, he's not
who you think he is.
- I'm not stupid, Kris!
I know what Vicente does
and what he's capable of.
But he loved my mother
and he loves me.
- That son of a
bitch is the reason
I spent 15 years on
the inside, okay?
He stole your mother from me!
- Bullshit! Bullshit!
I don't believe you.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait, just wait.
Jesus Christ, you really
do have my temper.
Just calm down.
Okay?
Look, there's a shop over there.
I think you should go and get
yourself a change of clothes
or something, I
don't know, a hoodie.
Can you do that?
- I don't know for sure
that you're father,
but I do have a temper.
- Did you know that
Vicente, your mom,
and I, we used to rob banks?
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
- What a joke.
Ha ha, super funny.
- No, seriously,
the three of us together,
we were quite the team.
Your mom would be on point,
okay, putting the guards
on their back foot with
her dazzling beauty,
and then Vicente and I
come rolling out the back
like a couple of bad parents.
We were good, fast.
Nobody ever got hurt, right?
That was your mom's number
one rule, and we stuck to it.
Ah.
You know when your mom got
pregnant with you, I panicked.
I mean, we'd just been
stealing and spending.
We didn't have any
savings, nothing.
So when Vicente suggested
we pull off one last
job, the big job,
I was all ears.
- So let me guess,
you got caught.
- No, job went off
without a hitch.
Free and clear with a huge
haul of cash.
It was beautiful.
- So how did you get caught?
- He set me up.
- Who?
- Vicente.
Left a trail of breadcrumbs
straight to my door.
Next thing I know,
I'm doing 15 years
and being ghosted
by the woman I love.
- That's seriously fucked up.
But that doesn't
mean he killed her.
- Dark one, bitch.
And some smokes.
- Ah!
- Hey!
And don't fuck it
up this time, bitch!
All right.
You know what?
She can still suck the
crumb off a trailer hitch.
Prime the pump a little.
Check out this slab of strange.
What a freak.
- Are you guys
having a good time?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- I'm gonna need your car.
- What?
You need my car?
Go fuck yourself,
cracking freak.
- I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
Can you repeat?
- Oh man.
This.
- I said go fuck
yourself.
Ah, you motherfucker!
Ah, help!
- It was your mom's
favorite song.
- Yeah.
- Did you know that, uh,
I bought your mom that necklace?
- Really?
- Yeah.
It was a present.
Do you know that diamonds
could cut through
anything and everything?
See, that was your mom.
She was strong and
beautiful like diamonds.
Like you.
- Do you ever see her again?
- Yeah.
One day, they, uh,
they told me I had a visitor.
Never got visitors, not once.
It was your mom. It was Leonor.
She tells me she's sorry she,
she didn't come
and see me sooner.
And she said it was
because of Vicente and me.
I figured as much.
And she says
she can't take it anymore.
She can't take this
life with Vicente
controlling her,
suffocating her.
She says she's gonna leave him
and she's gonna
take you with her.
And she tells me,
she says if anything
ever happens to her,
I need to come find my daughter
and I need to protect her.
Three weeks later, I get
word that she's dead.
Come on, we need to keep moving.
Come on.
- It's worse than I thought.
They had the devil
on their tail.
- Shit.
Right, come on, you
gonna help me or not?
Yes, get in, quick.
All right, look around and see
if you can find
a spare set of keys.
Otherwise, I'm gonna have
to hot-wire this guy.
Shit.
Hey,
you wanna give me that?
Give it to me.
- Now what?
- Okay.
- I'm not leaving
the country with you.
- Told your mom I'd
take you to your aunt's,
and that's what
I'm gonna do, okay?
- Aunt Carolina?
- Yeah, Aunt Carolina.
- She lives in America.
I haven't seen her
since I was a kid.
- Yeah!
Don't worry. You'll
be safe there.
- From who? From Vicente?
- Yeah, from Vicente.
- How do I know for sure that
you're telling me the truth?
Even if it is, even if
he did ruin your life,
he always made mine
really, really good.
- He killed your mom.
- You don't know that
for sure, you don't
have any proof.
- Look, your mom comes
and sees me in prison,
tells me she's gonna
take you and run.
Three weeks later, she's dead,
and you think that's
a coincidence?
I know him, okay?
I know what he's capable of.
- So do I!
My whole life.
And you know what?
A life I actually like.
I like where I live.
I like my school.
I like my friends.
And I already have
big plans for my life.
What are your plans, hmm?
What does deliver
me safely even mean?
Are you just, just going
to dump me on my aunts?
Leave again, not even
trying to be a good father!
- You know what?
Maybe you're right.
I mean, I spent your whole
life in a prison cell, right?
What the fuck would I know
about being a father anyway?
Aunt Carolina, she's a
good woman, all right?
She'll give you a good life.
- I have a good life.
I had a good life
without you in it.
- Okay.
- You don't care about me.
This is all about you, isn't it?
You and your personal
vendetta with Vicente.
- Hey!
Hey!
- Hey.
- Don't touch me!
Fuck you!
- Elisa!
- Fuck off.
Fuck off.
- Fuck off, go, go!
Hey, hey, hey! Shit.
Fuck!
Hey, stop.
- Shit.
Anyone?
Anyone? Anyone, hey!
Shit!
- Elisa!
- What are you looking at, hmm?
- Have you given yourself
a gift this week, Elisa?
- I don't like apples.
- Have you tried this apple?
- I'm not hungry.
- Just one bite.
- Give me that.
Fuck you, psycho!
- Elisa.
Elisa, where are you?
Elisa?
- Oh, Kris, Kris!
- Behind you.
Elisa, get down!
Get out of the way! Move!
- Do you consider
yourself a sharpshooter?
- Don't.
Let her go.
- Even if you put a
bullet through my brain,
the muscles will twitch
and pull the trigger.
- You wanna find out?
- Okay.
On three, you shoot.
If not, I will.
One, two, three.
- Okay!
Okay!
Please don't hurt her.
Don't hurt her, please.
- Walk towards me.
- No.
- Lie on the floor.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- Hands behind your back.
- No.
- Good.
Let's go, come on.
- Just do as he
says, Elisa, okay?
- Kris.
Kris.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no, it's
not your fault.
No!
- Who are you?
- Who the fuck are you?
- I ask the
questions, kidnapper.
Who are you?
- You fucking freak.
No! No!
- Who are you?
Who are you?
- No!
- Who are you?
Who are you?
- He's my father!
- Vicente's your father.
- No.
He's my real father.
- Interesting.
- What are you
gonna do with her?
- Compensation.
- Long time no see you, buddy.
Give me your gun.
I should have just
kill you back then.
- You need me.
- What?
- I don't see it.
I don't see it.
- We both wanna get Elisa back,
but you wanna live
through this, right?
I don't care about that.
I only care if she does.
I'll fight to the death
for her. You know me.
- She's not yours. I raised her.
- You killed her, you son of a
bitch!
- I didn't kill her. That's
all you need to know.
- Fuck you. You
took her from me.
When she finally got
wind of your bullshit
and tried to leave
you, you killed her.
Admit it.
- I took her from you
because that's what we did.
We took what we wanted.
- We robbed banks, Vicente.
- And I robbed you.
It's who we were.
What did you expect?
Honor among thieves, asshole?
- You took everything from me.
- That's because I
wanted everything.
Just fucking simple.
You used to understand that.
Hello?
Yes.
- You found my gift?
- Yes .
- Good.
Remember where you
tried to kill me?
- Yes.
- I'll be waiting.
Oh, before I forget,
please say thanks to
your right-hand man
for telling me that
the girl was in play.
- Ah.
- I know where she is.
- Who is that psycho?
It's not about money, is it?
No, it's personal to him.
You fuck him over too?
- I hired him for a job.
He came highly recommended,
a professional.
But he went beyond
what was required,
crossed the line.
- You tried to finish up
all the loose ends, right?
But you failed.
- We shot the fucker
with a tranquilizer dart
that would have taken
down a bull elephant.
He was taken to an
isolated location
and guarded by 15
of my best men.
I wanted to kill him myself.
When I arrived,
I found all my men dead.
His severed hand is still
cuffed to a railing.
They must have cuffed only
one of his hands, idiots.
What kind of will does
it take to do that?
To make that choice,
to carry that through.
And now, he's more
myth than man.
Devil that doesn't die.
Now, she's with
him because of you.
- What's going on?
What's the plan?
- He's not expecting you.
You come from the back,
like the old days.
You gonna give me a weapon?
- Flaco?
Flaco!
Fuck.
Where is she?
- You'll find out.
Move.
- Elisa, Elisa.
Elisa, Elisa, Elisa.
Hey.
Elisa, Elisa.
- Papi .
Papi .
- You're gonna need that.
- Puta !
- Girl's got nothing
to do with this.
You let her go.
- I'm sorry. I need her.
- Look, I don't give a fuck
about what happened
between you and Vicente, okay?
Let it go!
- You think Vicente killed her.
They hired me to
make her disappear.
I enjoyed it.
- He wanted it to
look like a suicide.
And yes, I got carried away.
Had some fun.
But at the end of the
day, I am what I am.
Now, he will have to
sacrifice what he loves
in order to know how it feels.
- No, no, no, no!
- No!
No! No!
No!
- Shit.
- No!
- Elisa!
- Kris, help! Kris!
Kris!
- Help me. I cannot stop this!
- No!
- Stop it. Stop it,
you motherfucker.
- Tell her how you did it,
and I'll tell you how
to stop the crane.
- What the fuck are you saying?
- I tried to stop your mom
from taking you away from me.
You understand?
She was going to
separate me from you.
- No!
- You have to say it.
- Okay.
- Say it!
- Okay, I pay you to kill her.
Are you happy now?
Is that what you wanted?
- No!
- Now, stop that
fucking thing now!
Stop that fucking thing, please.
Please.
- First floor.
I don't think you have
time to get there.
- Elisa, diamonds.
The diamonds.
- No, no, no!
- No! No!
- No!
No, no, no, no.
Kris, Kris, listen to me.
Kris, Kris.
No, please.
Please don't die, Kris.
Kris.
- Elisa.
Look at me.
- Kris, don't die.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
- You keep the promise to her.
- It was worth it.
- It was.
Dad.